《Here I Am》 - Dolly Parton
♪ Here I am, oh here I am ♪
♪ Here, here I am ♪
♪ If you need a love that's true ♪
♪ Need someone to stand by you ♪
♪ Here I am, oh here I am ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ If you need a helping hand, need someone to understand ♪
♪ Here I am, oh here I am ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ Here I am, I'm reaching out to give you love ♪
♪ That you're without ♪
♪ I can help you find what you've been looking for ♪
♪ Here I am, come to me, take my hand 'cause I believe ♪
♪ I can give you all the love you need and more ♪
♪ Oh here I am, here I am ♪
♪ Oh here I am, here, here I am ♪
♪ Here I am, I'm reaching
out to give you love ♪
♪ That you're without ♪
♪ I can help you find what you've been looking for ♪
莱斯利 能赢下这改变人生程度的大金额有什么感想吗
Leslie, how does it feel to win such a life-changing sum of money?
比昨天的心情好了一万倍
Oh, Well, I feel helluvalot better than yesterday.
我知道你选数字时得到了一点小帮助
I understand that you had a little help picking the winner number.
我永远都选同样的数字
- I picked the same ones I always do.
数字是你儿子的生日吗
- And that was your son's birthday?
没错 詹姆斯 我儿子詹姆斯
Yeah, James, my son James.
你想见他吗？
You wanna meet him?
当然啊 -好 詹姆斯
- Sure. Okay, James!
你打算用这十九万大钞做什么呢
And what do you plan to do with 190,000 smackeroos?
我也不知道 大概买栋房子吧
God, I don't know, maybe buy a house,
再给我儿子买点好的
and buy something nice for my boy.
好好享受人生
Just have a better life!
小莱 那我们呢
- Hey, Lee, what about us?!
还有我们呢
- What about us?
酒我请了！
- Drinks are on me! Whoa!
♪ Here I am, I'm reaching out ♪
致 莱 斯 利
♪ To give you love that you're without ♪
莱斯利 我知道你就在里面！
Leslie, I know you're in there!
（六年后）
谁也不准时付钱 怎么就莱斯利得搬走
- No one pays on time, but Leslie's gotta go?
就莱斯利得搬出去
Leslie's gotta go.
我能去哪啊
Where am I gonna go?
我还有这么多东西能去哪里啊
Where am I gonna take all this stuff?
没人准时给钱的吧
No one pays on time!
弗兰克？
Frank?
你能好心帮帮我吗
Hey, can you help me?
弗兰克 再一个月就好
Frank, just for a month.
一个月就好 弗兰克
Just for a month, Frank.
弗兰克！
Hey, Frank!
扎克 你给我过来
Zach, come here.
扎克 出来 扎克你个王八蛋
Zach! Come Zach, you motherfucker!
一晚 就一晚 就再住一晚也行啊
Hey, one night, one night, just tonight.
对不起我实在不能这么帮下去了
- I'm sorry I couldn't keep helping you.
你是要让我睡大街吗
- You're gonna put me on the street?
你这是要让我睡大街吗！
You're gonna put me on the fucking street?
开门啊 把这破门给我打开
Open the door, open the fucking door!
混蛋
Motherfucker!
我现在就拿上我的东西
Now, I'll be taking my things.
再送您一句 去你妈的
And saying, fuck you!
《Going Down》 - Freddie King
我要向下沉沦
♪ I'm going down ♪
我要向下 陨落 陷落 堕落 坠落 损落
♪ I'm going down, down, down,
down, down ♪
我要沉落
♪ Yes, I'm going down, yes ♪
我要向下 陨落 陷落 堕落 坠落 损落
♪ I'm going down, down, down,
down, down ♪
没错我就站在窗边
♪ Yes, I've got my big feet in the window ♪
头面向地面
♪ Got my head on the ground ♪
让我堕落
♪ Let me down ♪
关上那箱式车门
♪ And close that boxcar door ♪
让我回去我的查塔努加老家
♪ Well, I'm goin' back to Chattanooga ♪
睡在我姐妹的地板上
♪ And sleep on sister Irene's floor ♪
*詹姆斯*
妈
Mom.
嘿 - 嗨宝贝
Hey. -Hey, baby.
我有时会去那边喝咖啡
I get coffee there sometimes.
我给他们刷过点漆
I did some painting for them.
他们排骨做得蛮好
They do a mean ribs.
你喜欢在这里生活吗
You like living here?
嗯 当然
Yeah, sure.
大城市 有趣的事多得是
Big city, plenty of stuff going on.
你住哪里
And where do you stay?
我想着绕个远路
I thought we take the long way.
给你看看我的生活环境
Let you see where I'm living.
我就住在那边街角
I'm right around the corner.
就在这里
It's here.
哟哟哟
Yo, yo, yo!
嘿兄弟 还好吗？
Oh hey, bud, how's it going?
不错 那是你妈妈？
Good, this your moms? Alright.
对 这是我妈 莱斯利
Yeah, this is my mom, Leslie.
妈 这是维尔和克里斯 住在隔壁
Mom, that's Will and Chris, they're next door.
很高兴认识你 -很高兴认识你
- Pleased to know you. - Nice to meet you.
就是这里了
So this is it.
你可以睡我房间
Um, you can sleep in my room.
另一间是达伦的
That one's Darren's.
啊用不着 我睡沙发上就好
Oh God, no, I can sleep on the couch just fine.
没事的
No, that's okay.
你不告诉我是发生什么事了吗
You wanna tell me what's going on?
可不可以...
Oh, can't we...
在说我的破事之前
Can I hear about you first
我可以先听点你的事吗
before we start going into my shit?
好
Sure.
你想出去玩还是做点什么吗
You wanna go somewhere or something?
要不要出去玩
Wanna go out?
我太赶了没考虑 直接从工位上赶去接你的
I'm kinda beat, I came straight from work to get you.
好 那也许明天我们可以出去
Okay, well, maybe tomorrow we can go.
嗯好 我请个病假
Yeah, yeah, I'll call in sick.
没事不用特地麻烦的
No, you don't have to do that for me.
他们不介意的
They won't mind.
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
要不要吃点中餐
You want some Chinese?
我吃点吧
I could eat.
你还喜欢吃云吞面吗？
You still like wonton soup?
好 那我去买
Okay, I'll run to the corner.
你还好吗
You good?
我没事的 宝贝
Yeah, I'm fine, baby.
我不知道 她什么也还没跟我说
I don't know, she hasn't told me anything yet.
我也闻不出什么酒味
I can't smell it on her.
老实说 她状况确实不太好
I won't lie, she doesn't look good.
嗯我先挂了
Yeah, I gotta go.
外婆 她不会伤害我的
Grandma, she's not gonna hurt me.
挂了 我也爱你
I gotta go, I love you too.
好 再见
Okay, bye.
有看到哪件喜欢的吗
Did you find something you like?
嗯工作蛮稳定的
Yeah, work is steady.
工资一般也还不错
Pays decent enough most of the time.
达伦也在的
Darren's there too.
你喜欢这种工作吗？
You like that kinda work?
嗯 我喜欢在户外
Yeah, I like being outside.
我很在行
I'm good at it.
挺有趣的
It's funny,
我一直以为你会成为摇滚明星
I always thought you'd be a rock star.
什么时候开始以为的？
Since when?
从我给你买了那把吉他开始
Well, since I bought you that guitar.
你还有弹吗
You still play it?
不怎么了
Not so much anymore.
这几件怎么样
How about these?
不用 我来付 我来付
No, I'll get this, I'll get this.
没事啊
It's fine.
我还没到买内衣还要我儿子掏钱的地步呢
I don't need my son buying me underwear.
天包里真是乱死了
God, it's always such a mess in here!
真是
God.
你给你外婆打电话了？
Did you call your grandma?
打了
Yeah.
我猜你也会
I knew you would.
我说我们这天过得很开心 你也没事
I told her we were having a nice day, that you were good!
她没说你是个小谎话精？
Did she tell you you're a liar?
你有什么计划吗
So what's your plan?
我不知道 总之先陪你一段时间
I don't know, I'll spend some time with you.
怎么 这么快就想赶我走了？
Why? You want me to get out of here already?
没想过回家吗
What about going home?
你外婆外公家？想什么呢
To mom and dad? Are you out of your mind?
不是 我说以前的家
No, home.
啊 达奇和南希家啊
Oh, to Dutch and Nancy.
不了 正是因为他们我才来找你
No, they're the reason I am the way I am.
不回去
No.
你想去动物园吗
Hey, you wanna go to the zoo?
动物园 这类地方糟透了
The zoo? Those places are terrible.
我以前常带你去啊
I used to take you all time.
动物应该属于广阔的野外
Animals are meant to be in the wild
而我们却把它们都关进笼子里
and we put them in cages.
要是别人也围观你受苦你怎么想
How'd you like it if people stood around watching you suffer?
别人一直都围观啊
They do.
那就别去动物园啊
Then don't go to zoos.
妈 对不起
Mom! I'm so sorry.
别这样
Stop!
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?
你有用那些约会软件吗
You on one of them dating apps?
挑女孩子就像用炸药炸鱼一样眼花缭乱
Picking out girls like youse fishing with dynamite?
我没那种时间
I don't have time for that.
你连玩乐的时间都没有？
Don't have time to have fun?
我还有工作呢 这些不着急
I'm working, trying to put back.
啊你在做我以前没能做到的事
Ah, you're trying to do what I didn't do.
庆幸我还是给你教会了点东西
Well, I'm glad I taught you something.
在我出房间之前 我需要和你过一遍基本规则
Before I leave, I wanna go over some ground rules.
啊好啊
Oh, okay.
只要你能定个计划就能留在这里
You can stay here as long as you need to make a plan.
你需要多久都可以
Long as you need.
但是不能永远住在这里
But you can't live here.
你要有个计划
You need a plan.
好
Okay.
以及禁止喝酒
And no drinking.
宝贝 我都不喝酒了
Baby, I don't drink no more.
可以吸点大麻 没关系 但是
We can smoke pot, that's fine, but-
宝啊 我已经不像以前那样嗜酒了
- Baby, I don't drink like I used to.
好
Okay
那明天见
see you tomorrow?
晚安
Good night.
我傍晚六点左右回来
I'll be home around 6:00.
之后我们可以出去散散步什么的
Just, we can take a walk or something.
我自己没事的
I'll be just fine.
好
Okay.
还好吗
How's it going?
我叫莱斯利 我是詹姆斯他妈妈
Hi! I'm Leslie, I'm James's mama.
啊我记得
Oh, I remember.
今天是要出去吗
Heading out for the day?
嗯 给他买点牛奶
Well, yeah, he needs some milk.
是小詹姆喝麦片粥要配牛奶吗
Oh, little Jimmy needs milk for his cereal?
过得愉快
Well, have a good one!
谢谢你女士
Thank you, ma'am.
不行不行不行
No, no, no, no!
不能在这里喝 别在这里喝
Not in here, not in here!
要喝出去喝
Take that outside!
不行不行不行 快出去
No, no, no, get out!
谢谢你宝贝
Oh, thank you, honey.
兄弟 要是我递大麻卷给我妈 那我妈呼死我不可
Man, my mama whoop me good if I passed her a joint.
你妈妈在哪 达伦
Where's your mama, Darren?
她过世了
She passed away.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
人生就是烂
Yeah, life sucks.
你别笑他 他这么伤心
Don't you laugh at him, he's sad.
你喜欢陪在詹姆斯身边吗
You like to be around James?
太爱了
Oh, I love it.
你们上次见面是多久以前了
When's the last time you all saw each other?
一定有六年了吧
It must been six years.
天 六年？怎么会
Damn, six years? How come?
你能别多管闲事了吗 真是
Hey, will you mind your own business? Jesus.
他没做错啊
He's fine.
他不需要像我妈妈教训我一样上拖鞋才听话
He don't need me riding him the way my mama rode me.
是说詹姆斯外婆吗
That's James's grandma?
她是什么样的
What's she like?
浸信会信徒
Baptist.
她就说了句“浸信会信徒”
She said, "Baptist."
你们俩真好玩
You two are funny.
去达奇和南希家住有什么不好
I mean, what's wrong with going to Dutch and Nancy's?
他们都很坏
Those people are evil.
他们很好的
They're fine.
你不像我一样了解他们
You don't know 'em like I do.
你还好吗
Are you good in here?
怎么了？
What?
我就是磕嗨了而已
I'm just stoned, is all.
晚安 宝贝
Night night, sweetie.
晚安
Good night.
妈？
Mom?
混蛋
Motherfucker.
你见过我妈吗
Hey, you seen my mom?
没有啊 怎么了
No, everything okay?
克里斯？你也没见过？
Chris? Nothing?
没有
No.
没发生什么吧
Everything alright?
看到的话给我打电话就行
Just call me if you do.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
你今天回家很早嘛
Well, you're home early!
我全镇子里找遍你了
I've been all over town looking for you.
我没出去啊 就这里看电视
I was here, baby, watching TV.
妈
Mom?!
我本来在的 然后出去走了走
I was here and I went for a walk
在这里待着有点闷得慌
'cause I've been cooped up in here.
所以出去找工作了
So I went looking for a job.
找工作？ -嗯
- A job? - Yeah.
得找个计划 不对 想个计划
Gonna get my plan - you know, figure out my plan.
怎么了吗 你还好吗
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?
宝贝 你还好吗
Honey, are you okay?
找的哪种工作
What kind of job?
哪种工作？
What kind?
什么都找啊
Any kind!
什么都行
Any kind.
你刚才是在隔壁吗
Were you next door?
真的够了
Jesus fucking Christ!
宝贝 宝贝 宝贝
Baby, baby, baby!
宝贝 哎呀
Baby? Oh!
她之前是不是在这里
Was she in here-
兄弟 你看是这样 - 我之前问你的时候
- Hey, man, look- - When I was talking to you?
我们就只是喝了杯啤酒
We was just having a beer.
你和我妈一起喝啤酒？
You were having a beer with my mother?
这能算事吗
I didn't know that was a problem.
那你为什么要说谎
No? Then why'd you lie about it?
因为她听到你时慌了啊
Because she freaked when she heard you.
我不知道你们之间有什么问题
Okay, I don't know what's going on between you two-
别再和她搭话了 别再找她了！
- Don't talk to her again! Don't talk to her again!
你冷静一点
Dude, you need to calm down!
宝贝？宝贝 宝贝
Baby? Baby, baby.
宝贝求你了 我就是出去了
Baby, please, I went out.
我只是想找点乐子而已
I was just trying to have some fun, 'cause it's-
你偷了达伦的钱
- You stole money from Darren.
什么？
What?
你偷了达伦的钱啊
You stole money from Darren.
我没有
I didn't steal.
他告诉你的？
Did he tell you that?
你别给我说谎了！
Come on, lie to me again. Lie to me again!
我是你妈妈 我不会偷你的钱啊
I'm your mother, I would not steal money from you.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
放开我
Get off of me.
真他妈不敢相信
Un-fucking-believable!
你这个嘴巴漏风的杂种！
You fucking chicken shit!
宝贝
Hey! Baby?
我不是说过了吗 禁止喝酒！
What did I say?! No drinking!
我是你母亲 你不能用这种口吻和我说话 詹姆斯 -我母亲？
I'm your mother, you cannot talk to me this way, James. -Mother?
我母亲？！
Mother?!
没错 是你妈妈
Yes, your momma
你就是个酒鬼！-快别这样了
You're a drunk! -stop it.
我很难受啊
I am sick.
我不要再经历一次了 我不要
I'm not gonna do this again, I'm not.
你自己？那我呢？
You? What about me?
我们应该享受人生的
We were supposed to have a good life.
我也不想让你过成这样啊
I didn't want this for you.
在你来之前我都过得很好
I had a good life until you showed up.
我都不够二十岁
I'm not even 20.
我连合法喝酒的年龄都没到 还要反过来照顾我妈？
I can't even drink yet, and I have to take care of my mother?
我还得照顾你？
I have to take care of you?
我就定了一条规则 禁止喝酒
I made one rule, no drinking,
而你他妈连一天都坚持不下来！
and you couldn't last a fucking day!
我太伤心了
I'm sad.
我忍不住啊
I can't help it.
但我真的很想做一个好妈妈
But I wanna be a good momma.
我想再当一次好妈妈
I wanna be a good momma again.
我真的很想当一个合格的妈妈 我真的
Baby, I wanna be a good momma, I do.
我那么爱你
I love you so much, baby.
你在给谁打电话？
Who are you calling?
你在给你外婆打电话吗
Are you calling grandma?
你不准给我妈打电话！
You do not call my mother!
她是我母亲！
She is my mother!
你没有资格联络她！
You do not call my mother!
你别给我把她拽进来！
You leave her out of this!
你在下面说什么了 为什么警察来了
What are you doing? Why are they here?
带你去汽车站
Taking you to the bus station.
不要啊宝贝
No baby.
我再也不出去了 宝贝
I will not go out again, baby.
我联系达奇了
I called Dutch.
达奇？
Dutch?
你回镇子了他会去接你
He's gonna pick you up when you get to town.
宝贝别赶我回去
Baby don't make me go back there.
不要 不要
No, no.
你和你外婆没两样！
You're just like your grandma!
宝贝
Baby
我真的很爱你
I love you so much.
不要这样对我
Don't do this to me.
希望这够你喝个够了
I hope that fills your cup.
嗨
Hi.
嗯 就是把钱分开投到了两个地方 结果哪边都没收回来
Yeah, it's just putting money down on two different places and never got that back.
车也被偷了 破事一桩接一桩
My car got fucking stolen and shit just piled up.
那么久你都没去工作？
All that time, you weren't working?
我有在工作
I was.
你过得还好吗南希
Well, how are you doing, Nance?
行吧
Alright.
詹姆斯已经把事情都告诉我们了
James told us what happened.
住手
Stop!
继续啊 拿吧
Go on, go ahead.
快拿
Go ahead.
自便
Help yourself.
就像你平常一样
You always do.
我们同意接你回来 完全是看在那孩子
The only reason we agreed to put you up is that boy,
和我们以前的关系上
and what you did for us.
你别给她脸上贴金
Don't you give her that!
那你来说？
Do you want to do this?
我们为这个家付出的可比她
We put a helluva lot more to this place
给的多了百倍
than what she gave us.
你还能在这的唯一原因
The only reason you're here
只是因为那孩子
is James.
但是你不能像以前对那孩子一样做事
But there will be none of that shit you pulled on him.
这是我的房子 你要遵守我的规则
This is my house, you will follow my rules.
达奇 别这么说嘛
Dutch, don't talk like that.
我没在和你打哈哈 不然我把你扔马路上去
I ain't fucking around, Lee, I'll put you on the curb!
达奇 是我啊
Dutch, it's me.
你们今晚有什么安排吗
What y'all doing tonight?
我们要生篝火
We're having a fire.
你可不可以帮我个忙
Would you do me favor
别和任何人说我回来了
and you just don't tell anyone I'm here?
南希已经说出去了
Nance already did.
你可以随时来加入 但记得明天还要让你去刷漆
You're welcome to join, but you will be painting tomorrow,
所以还是多休息会比较好
so you might wanna think about getting some rest.
让我刷漆
I'm painting?
是啊 开始入门
Yeah, yeah, to start with.
小莱 我们可不是在做慈善
This ain't a charity, Lee.
我们可不是让别人碎嘴的废物
We ain't them derelicts you spit on,
我们也不再只会玩乐了
and we ain't partying no more.
我们会工作 回家休息之后 继续工作
We work, when we come home, we work some more.
所以我不会再说第二次了
So don't expect a repeat.
你可没有下一次机会让你浪费了 懂了吗
Ain't no one taking your shit a second time, you got it?
是你自己说的还是南希让你说的
Is that you talking or is that Nancy talking?
要出去你自己知道门在哪
You know where the door is.
你开玩笑的吧
Are you fucking kidding me?
真没有 -她就像条鱼
- No. - Man, she was a fish.
是啊 - 你还记得
- Yeah. - You remember that?
她能把你们都喝倒
- She could drink all of ya'll under the table.
厉害
Hell yeah.
她就把钱都那么浪费了
She just blew all that money?
是啊 没错
- Yeah. - Yeah.
没错
Yeah.
她去哪了
Where's she been?
你可以直接问本人啊
Well, why don't we ask her?
好
Yeah.
快去
Go.
莱斯利？ - 别这样
- Leslie? - No, don't.
皮特 你别把她叫出来
Pete, no, don't you call her out!
莱斯利？
Leslie?
Leslie
我知道你在的
I know you're in there
那就是她的早餐
That was breakfast.
天啊 你声音能不能低点
Oh my God, lower your fucking voice!
我才不管
I don't care.
让她听啊
She fucking hears that.
你看我在乎吗
I can give two fucking shits!
我恨不得她能听到才好
I hope she fucking does!
你要怎么才够 是要我揍她一顿才甘心吗
What do you want! You want me to knock her around for you?
扁一顿才行？
Pop her in the mouth?
才不是 我要她给我他妈滚出去
No, I want her out of my fucking house!
你自己不赶啊
Who's fucking stopping you!
是你让瘟神住在这的啊
You're the one who let her in here!
那孩子哭着给我打电话 一直在求我
He called me crying, he was begging on the phone.
我除了同意还能怎么办
What the fuck was I supposed to do
我不能再被她耍了
I will not be played for a fool, not again.
我不忍了！你别给我走 达奇
No, I will not! Don't you walk away from me, Dutch!
达奇 你这个混蛋给我回来
Dutch, get back here you fucking asshole.
《I Don't Need your Rockin' Chair》 - George Jones
♪ I don't need your rockin' chair ♪
♪ Your Geritol or your Medicare ♪
♪ Well, I still got Neon in my veins ♪
♪ This grey hair don't mean a
thing ♪
♪ I do my rockin' on the stage ♪
♪ You can't put this possum in a
cage ♪
♪ My body's old but it ain't
impaired ♪
我可以点酒了
You can set me up.
♪ I don't need your rockin'
chair ♪
♪ I ain't ready for the junkyard
yet ♪
♪ 'Cause I still feel
like a new corvette ♪
♪ It might take a little
longer but I'll get there ♪
谢谢
Thank you.
♪ Well, I don't need your
rockin' chair ♪
♪ I don't need your rockin'
chair ♪
♪ Your Geritol or your Medicare ♪
♪ I still got Neon ♪
《Highwayman》 - The Highwaymen
♪ Along the coach roads I didride ♪
♪ With sword and pistol by my side ♪
♪ Many a young maid lost her baubles to my trade ♪
♪ Many a soldier shed his life blood on my blade ♪
♪ The bastards hung me in the spring of '25 ♪
♪ But I am still alive ♪
♪ I was a sailor, I was born upon the tide ♪
♪ And with the sea I did abide ♪
♪ I sailed a schooner 'round the horn to Mexico ♪
♪ I went aloft to furl the mainsail in a blow ♪
你好呀 你好
Howdy. Howdy!
嗯
Yeah.
♪ And when the yards broke off, ♪
♪ They said that I got killed ♪
♪ But I am living still ♪
那杯是我的吧
I think that one was mine.
大概确实是吧
I think you might be right.
抓了个正着
Gotcha.
啊真是的
Oh, you did.
嗯
Yeah.
两位是从哪来的
So where are you boys from?
你们在给萨姆森打理农场吗
Are you cowboying for Samson?
我们来自杰克逊维尔
We're in from Jacksonville.
只是过客啊 挺好
Just passing through, that's nice.
只是过客
Just passing through.
那你对我们这个小桃源乡有什么想法吗
And what do you think of our little piece of paradise here?
是个好地方
It's a fine town.
我土生土长
Well, I was born here
所以我告诉你这不是什么好地方
and I can tell you it ain't fine.
是吗
Is that so?
是啊 但我在这里赢了彩票呢
Yeah, but I did win the lottery here.
没错 就在这个酒吧
Yeah, right here in this bar.
是吗
Did you?
那可真幸运
That's pretty lucky.
是呢 他们以前还把我照片挂吧台上面呢
Yep, they used to have my picture above the bar,
但是现在看不到了
but I can't see it no more.
先生 这位先生
Mister? Hey, mister?
先生 我的照片呢
Mister, where's my picture?
我们这不提供照片 只有酒杯或酒瓶
We don't serve picture, just glass or bottle.
我的照片呢
Where's my picture?
记得我吗
My face
我赢了彩票的
I won the lottery.
我就是那个赢了彩票的
I was the one who won the lottery.
奥贝以前把照片挂那里的啊
Obe used to have it up there.
那我也不知道啊
Yeah, I don't know.
我接手了奥贝的酒吧
I bought it from Obe.
啊？然后你就把它摘了？
What? And you just took it down?
我相信你当时一定拍了不少照片
I'm sure you have plenty of photographs of that day.
啊谢谢
Well, thank you
是韦伦的歌哎
sweet Waylon.
你要来和我跳舞吗
Do you wanna dance with me?
来吧 快来吧
Come on. Come on.
来嘛 来跳舞
Come on, let's dance.
♪ Lord, it's the same old tune ♪
《Are You Sure Hank Done It This Way》 - Waylon Jennings
快嘛 我知道你想跳的
Come on, you wanna dance.
♪ Fiddle and guitar ♪
哎呀
Oh, no.
快站起来嘛 - 真的不用
- Get up! - I insist.
是非得我握着你的手吗
Have I gotta drag you by the hand...?
♪ Rhinestone suits and new shiny cars ♪
♪ Is Been The same way for years ♪
♪ We need a change ♪
♪ Somebody told me, when I came to Nashville ♪
♪ Son, you finally got it made ♪
你很会跳舞啊
You got some moves.
是啊 我以前每天晚上都来的
Yeah, I used to come here every night.
小伙子们都排队等我
Had all the boys lining up.
♪ But I don't think Hank done it this way ♪
♪ Take it home ♪
谢谢你的好意 小姐
Thanks for the dance, miss.
你可以继续跳啊
No, you can stay.
来嘛 和我多待一会喝点酒
Come on, you can stay and buy me a drink.
祝你今晚愉快
Have a good night and be well.
♪ Speedin' my young life away ♪
♪ Tell me one more time just so's I'll understand ♪
♪ Are you sure Hank done it this way ♪
♪ Did old Hank really do it this way ♪
喂
Hey.
♪ Lord, I've seen the world, with a five piece band ♪
♪ Looking at the back side of me ♪
♪ Singing my songs and one of his now and then ♪
♪ But I don't think Hank done 'em this way ♪
♪ I don't think Hank done it this way ♪
你看什么看啊你
What're you standing around looking at?
♪ Take it home ♪
无聊死了
Boring.
真无聊
南希 你猜我碰见哪位贵人了
Hey, Nance, guess who I saw?
你这个杀千刀的！
You motherfuckers!
你们这帮冷血动物！
You fucking monsters!
南希 去你妈的
Fuck you, Nancy!
好了 该走了
Alright, come on!
我看到你了
I see you over there.
快起床了
Rise and shine!
该行动了
Let's go.
这里不是让你休息的地方 快走吧
Get up and get off the property, come on.
快行动
Let's go!
这可不是让你睡觉的地方
This ain't no place to sleep.
就这样
That's it.
找到这么个东西
Hey man, I found this.
是什么
Oh, yeah?
我也不知道
I don't know.
你拿过来我让我干嘛
What am I gonna do with that?
你自己看 要么翻翻看有没有什么有用的
I don't know, go through it and see what you find
剩下的都扔了吧
and junk the rest, I guess.
我这里成失物招领处了 行吧
Lost and found now? Okay.
你干嘛呢 罗亚尔
Whoa! Jesus, Royal.
真是的
Come on, man.
我就听说她回来了
I heard she was back.
我认识她吗
Do I know her?
她是在你离开之前...
She came before you left...
不对 是你来了她刚好走了
I mean, she left for you came.
很悲惨的故事
Real sad story, real sad.
你好啊 小莱
Well heya, Lee.
在等人吗
Waiting for someone?
还是说想喝杯酒？
You looking for a drink?
薯条配汉堡不是不行 但伏加特配薯条？
Beer and burgers, I get, but vodka and French fries?
服了 味道怎么样
Shit, how's that taste?
我记得当时可迷你了
Yeah, I remember when I went tits up for you.
所有人都在为了钱讨好你
Everyone cozying up, all that money.
但你也有错
But you ain't without fault.
我说的事情你都清楚
I ain't saying nothing you don't know.
我现领残疾补贴了 这你确实不清楚
I'm on disability now, that's new.
你看着挺好啊
You look fine to me.
我挺好看？
I look fine?
我说表面不像有事
I mean, not broken.
你要做什么 皮特
What are you doing, Pete?
你干嘛啊
What are you doing?
靠
Dammit.
啊糟了
Oh, shit, man.
那位小姐回来找她的包了
That lady's back looking for her bag.
你现在拿出去她一定会知道你翻过了
You bring it out there, she gonna know you went through it.
就这样不管了吧
Better let her be, man.
别管了
Just let her be.
真是
Shit.
这位小姐
Hey, hey, lady.
怎么
What?
你不会轻易放弃啊 是吗
You're just not gonna quit, are ya?
我没回你电话是因为
The reason I'm not returning your calls is because-
啊？
- What?
靠
Shit.
我什么都没偷啊
I didn't steal nothing.
我知道我知道
I know. I know.
我接到过你的电话
I got your calls.
但是没回你
I didn't return them,
你需要的话现在工作给你了 好吗
but the job is yours if you want it, alright?
时薪十块
Pays 10 an hour.
还是这样吧 算成七块比较好
You know what? Make it seven.
时薪七块一小时 包吃住
Seven an hour, room and board.
你要的话现在可以上班了 行吗
The job is yours if you want it, okay?
很轻松的 时薪七美元
It's easy work, $7 an hour.
你只需要打理客房就好了
All you got to do is maintain the property,
跑点小差事 包吃住
run some errands, room and board.
你有什么要说的吗
Did you wanna say something?
你要给我工作？
You're offering me a job?
是啊 你一直打电话问的工作
Yeah, the one you've been calling about.
我打过电话？
I was calling?
不是吗
I thought so.
好
Okay.
好吧
Okay. Shit.
你为什么一直在说脏话
Why do you keep cussing?
一小时后在办公室见我就行了
Just meet me over at the office in an hour
我给你安排工作
and I'll get you set up.
你是刚把她聘回来了？
Did you just offer her a job?
我也不知道自己是怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me, man.
我建议你现在出去然后收回刚才的话
Look, you better go back out there and tell her no.
你去说！
You go tell her!
真是的 斯威尼 你让她睡哪啊
Dammit, Sweeney! Where's she gonna sleep?
睡我房间
In my room.
那你呢
Where are you gonna sleep?
我睡你房间？
In your room?
那我要睡哪
And where am I fitting to sleep?
就是这里了
Right in here.
接了有线电视
Now, you got your basic cable.
还有无线网 虽然不一定所有时候都有网
You got Wi-Fi, most days you got Wi-Fi.
这个是你的吧
I think this is yours.
啊抱歉 对是我的
Oh, I'm sorry, it is mine,yeah.
那我要做什么才行
So what have I got to do for all this?
什么都不需要！不对
Oh, well, nothing! I mean-
我得工作才行 是吧
- I gotta work, don't I?
啊对 是的
Oh, right, yeah.
嗯 你得工作
Yeah, you gotta work.
基本上就清理房间
Basically, you got to clean upthe rooms
房客离开以后洗毛巾洗床单
after the guests leave and wash the towels, wash the sheets,
清理一下客房
maintain the property a little bit
还有给房客拿一下行李什么的
and help guests with their bags.
就这些？
That it?
嗯 基本上就是全部工作了
That is it, really,pretty much it, right.
那好
Okay.
今晚不用做什么 明天正式开始
And nothing tonight, we'll start tomorrow.
那更好！
Okay!
好
Okay.
另一个人叫罗亚尔
Royal, the other one of us,
我们快吃饭了
we're about to have supper,
你要来一起吃的话随时欢迎
if you wanna join us, you're more than welcome.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但我还是先收拾收拾吧
I think I'm gonna settle in.
嗯也对 那我就不打扰你了
Right, of course, I'll leave you to it.
好了 啊对了
Alright. Hey?
嗯？
Yeah.
大概什么时候发工资？
When do I get paid?
啊对 这个也挺重要的
Right, of course, that's pretty important.
每周末
End of the week.
但你需要预支的话 我应该
But if you needed an advance, I could probably...
那再好不过了
It would help.
嗯好
Right, okay.
没问题
Not a problem.
先给五十美元怎么样？
How's 50? Is that...
啊 太多啦
No, God.
谢谢
Thank you!
嗯好 所以就这样
Okay, alright. So, great.
那晚安了
Well, good night then.
晚安 我们明天见
Good night, I'll see you tomorrow.
一定的 明天一定见
Yes, you will, you will.
好梦 晚安
Sleep well. Yeah, good night.
真是 闹钟没响
Damn clock didn't go off.
没事的
Hey, look, it's okay.
你也不知道几点起 我又没告诉你
You didn't know, I didn't tell you,
不过还是说一下是早上八点开始
but we start at 8:00 AM around here.
了解
Good to know.
这样吧
Alright. You know what?
我给你拿串钥匙 这样你就可以去其他房间了
Let me get you a key so you can get into the other rooms.
真是 怎么拆不下来
Oh, come on, come on.
谢谢你 -好了拿着吧
- Thank you.- Why don't you take that.
真谢谢你
Thank you.
罗亚尔 你还记得我吗
Hi, Royal! You remember me?
记得
I do.
过得怎么样
How you doing?
行吧
Okay.
那我现在就开始干活
Well, I'll get to it.
好 - 拜
- Okay.- Bye.
有需要的话找我就行
If you need anything, let me know.
一定
Sure.
罗亚尔 你见过一个这么大的紫色行李箱吗
Hey, Royal, you seen a pink suitcase about so big?
她会慢慢熟悉起来的
Hey, she'll get the hang of it, man.
打扫个房间
Cleaning the room.
难于上青天哦
Real mountain to climb.
还有一点是可以用你的手指
A good way is to use your finger, okay?
还有东西黏着的话再擦一次就行了
And if there's guck on it, then you need to do it again.
我也不想显得太苛刻 莱斯利 - 没有的
I mean, I don't wanna be a hard-ass, Leslie -No.
但扫除就是要干净
But clean is clean.
嗯对
Yeah, yeah,
我感觉我也慢慢开始了解这里怎么运作了
I guess I'm just getting used to how things work around here.
嗯我们尽量一次就做好
Yeah, we do it right the first time around.
好的了解
Okay, yes, sir.
那好
Okay, alright then.
那晚安
Well, good night.
嘿 那个 我可以
Hey, hey, hey, can I...
我可以拿另外一半的预支吗
Could I have the other half of that advance
昨晚剩下的？
that you gave me?
之前的一半我拿去买日用品了然后
'Cause I spent the first half on groceries, and I
我想要是能再给房间
was thinking it'd be so nice
放点花装饰一下就更好了
to have some flowers for the room.
给你
There you go.
感谢
Thank you.
那好
Alright.
达奇呢 南希
Where's Dutch, Nance?
怎么 你有种把我赶出你那破家
What, you got the balls to throw me out you fucking house,
但没种直视我？
but you can't look at me?
小姑娘 好歹看看你是在哪里吧
Little girl, you need to look around.
小姑娘？
Little girl?
那我确实比陈年老菜强
You fucking wish.
你用不着担心我
You don't gotta worry about me
因为不管你费多大力气我也不会离开的
because despite your best effort, I ain't going nowhere.
我有工作了
I got me a job.
我还有地方住 所以你最好也注意点
I got a place to stay, so you better watch out.
你们都还记得莱斯利吧
Y'all remember, Leslie, don't you?
海伦和莱蒙德家的女孩？
Helen and Raymond's little girl?
对啊 我们镇里的幸运彩票赢家
That's right, our lucky lotto winner!
你还记得布里克曼家吗
You remember the Brickmans?
布里克曼夫妻和沃伦帕内尔
Mr. and Mrs. Brickman and Warren Parnell.
他以前礼拜日时在教堂演奏管风琴
He used to play Sunday Organ.
他们一定非常想听你的人生轶事呢
I'm sure they'd love to hear what's going on in your life.
要不坐这来？
Why don't you pull up a seat?
你还好吗
How are you?
你不在有一段时间了
You disappeared on us.
我？没事啊
Me? I'm fine.
你家人呢 我还挺想念他们的
And your folks? I do miss them.
嗯 他们挺好的
Yeah, they're well.
他们就住在弗罗里达
They're down in Florida.
下次你见到他们的话 记得帮忙给我问个好
Next time you speak to 'em, tell 'em I'm thinking of 'em.
当然会
Oh, I will.
莱斯利
You know, Leslie,
我们现在也还在为你祈祷
we still pray for you.
不管以前发生过什么
No matter what's been done,
教堂的门一直为你打开
the church is still here for you.
我希望你会记得
I hope you know that.
抱歉打扰你们了
sorry for the interruption.
我希望大家能度过一个美好的夜晚 上帝保佑
And I hope you all have a good night and God bless.
还有啊
And ya know,
我就在这边呢
I'm just gonna be over here
你们要是受够了干瘪老白菜的话可以来
enjoying myself, if you get tired of ole saddle bags here.
回头见啊 小莱
See you around, Lee.
当然
Yeah, you will.
实在抱歉
I apologize.
那就是我妈说的耕完田的老驴
That's what my mama would call rode hard and hung up wet.
早安 天真是 闹钟又没响
Morning. God, damn alarm didn't go off again.
罗亚尔 你能告诉他我真的是那种没响吗
Royal, will you tell him my alarm didn't go off?
真的不是我的错
I can't do nothing about that.
有些人就是不懂珍惜
Some people can't see a good thing
盘子上的好菜
when it's dropped on their plate.
怎么了吗
Everything go okay?
我打赌你一粒灰尘都找不到
I dare you to find dirt.
好了废柴们 要么喝了要么倒掉 马上关门了
Alright, derelicts, chug it or fuck it... last call.
《Are You Sure》 - Willie Nelson
看看你的身旁
♪ Look around you ♪
看看你所在的酒吧
♪ Look down the bar from you ♪
看看那些面庞
♪ At the faces that you see ♪
你确定这是你渴望造访的地方吗
♪ Are you sure that this
is where you want to be? ♪
这是在开玩笑吗
Is that a joke?
那是你的朋友们
♪ These are your friends ♪
但他们是真感情吗
♪ But are they real friends? ♪
他们是真心爱你吗
♪ Do they love you as much as me? ♪
你确定这是你渴望造访的地方吗
♪ Are you sure that this is where you want to be? ♪
你似乎并没有准备好
♪ You seem in such a hurry ♪
来面对这样的生活
♪ To lead this kind of life ♪
你经历过那么多的痛苦与悲伤
♪ And you've caused so many pain and misery ♪
看看你所处的境地 好好瞧一瞧
♪ But look around you, take a good look ♪
这话只在你我之间
♪ Just between you and me ♪
你确定这是你渴望造访的地方吗
♪ Are you sure that this is where you want to be? ♪
请不要让我以泪相劝
♪ Please don't let my tears persuade you ♪
我本无意落泪
♪ I had hoped I wouldn't cry ♪
但眼泪却滴落不止
♪ But lately, teardrops seem a part of me ♪
看看你自己 好好瞧一瞧
♪ But look around you, take a good look ♪
只剩孤独一人的自己
♪ At all the local used-to-be's ♪
你确定这是你渴望造访的地方吗
♪ Are you sure that this is where you want to be ♪
嗨 小兄弟
Hey, buddy.
你现在不睡觉乱跑啥呢
What are you doing up and out of bed?
我以前就住在这里
I used to live here.
没错哦
Yeah
请问有事吗
Can I help you?
需要我带你出去吗
Do I need to walk you out?
不 不用
No, no.
这真是栋好房子啊
God, this was a good house.
我以前在这里做饭打扫
I used to cook and clean.
我以前还做饭打扫
还有圣诞节 我们以前过圣诞时最开心了了
And Christmas, we used to have a just wonderful Christmas.
我们以前就把圣诞树放在那个角落
We used to put the tree there in that corner.
你们现在也放这里吗
Is that where you put your tree?
需要我帮忙给你联系什么人吗
Is there somebody that you need me to call?
不用的
No.
女士 真的不需要我帮忙给你联系其他人吗
Ma'am, is there somebody that you need me to call?
莱斯利
Hey, Leslie.
听着 我很抱歉你不适合做这个工作
Listen, I'm sorry it didn't work out.
你可以把我之前给的钱算成工资的
You can just take what I gave you for the time you put in.
莱斯利？
Leslie?
我觉得她不在里面
I don't think she in there.
莱斯利 我有话要跟你说
Hey, Leslie, I need to talk to you.
快来
Come on.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我最近都不在状态
I haven't been myself late-.
是我一直以来都不在状态
For a long time
这是份好工作 我深知
And this is a good job, I understand that.
而且我搞砸了 真的很对不起
And I messed up, I'm sorry.
你有能联系的人的话 我可以载你过去
If you got people, I can take you to 'em.
要是有的话
If I had,
我昨晚就会打给他们了
I'da called 'em last night.
我对你来说也许只是个烂好人
I might look stupid to you but-
你不是
- You don't.
我也不是那种随便能被人踩在头上的人
Yeah, well, I ain't one for letting people get over on me.
我差点就信你了
You could've fooled me there.
听着 也许看不出来
Look, it might not be obvious to you,
但我很想继续在这里工作
but I'm asking to stay.
那间屋子打扫完以后去找罗亚尔
When you finish that, go check in with Royal.
16号房后面有些垃圾 他需要帮忙收拾
There's some crap behind 16, he needs help sorting.
是罗亚尔 我们也不介意他
Royal. We like to keep him around.
还能吓跑小孩子
Something for the kids to poke a stick at.
你酗酒有多久了
How long you been drinking?
好吧 不用我多管闲事？
Okay, mind my business?
没问题
Sure thing.
他可做过比这还要怪的事情呢 罗亚尔
Royal, that's not even the weirdest thing he does.
你之后会碰到的
You'll see in time.
之后自己会见到
You'll see for yourself.
他就脱光衣服在那片空地乱跑
He'll get butt-naked and run that field
乱叫 像个野生动物一样
just screaming like a damn wild man.
真的很疯
It's crazy, man!
他就半夜出去 然后裸奔
He'll just go, just running naked, crazy!
你之后就看到的
You wait till you'll see it.
那帮警察都懒得搭理他了已经
Oh, man, the cops don't even bother with him anymore.
因为手指头都数不清了
He does it so damn much.
真是个疯子
Crazy son of a bitch.
那个
You know...
忽然戒瘾对身体影响很大的
quitting cold turkey, it's a good way to shock your system.
我也没得选啊
Well, I don't got a choice.
是有人逼你戒了吗
Someone making you quit?
好吧 你看着也不想说这事 没关系
Alright, well, you don't seem like you wanna talk and that's okay,
但我们现在正吃饭呢
but we're trying to eat dinner here
我也不想听外面的那声音
and I don't wanna listen to that.
有什么喜欢的音乐吗 我可以放
So is there some music you'd like me to put on?
你随便选
You can pick.
好吧 那就来看看
Okay, why don't we just play
罗亚尔放着什么吧
whatever Royal's got on there?
让我们DJ罗亚尔来点歌
Just let ol' D.J. Royal spin it
♪ Hare Krshna, Hare Krshna ♪
什么嘛
What is that?
他可真是疯得彻底
Oh, man, he's out of his mind.
♪ Hare Rama, Hare Rama ♪
不差倒是 不难听
It's not bad, though, it's not bad.
♪ Rama Rama, Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Krshna, Hare Krshna ♪
♪ Krshna Krshna, Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Rama, Hare Rama ♪
♪ Rama Rama, Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Krshna, Hare Krshna ♪
♪ Krshna Krshna ♪
♪ Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Rama, Hare Rama ♪
♪ Rama Rama, Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Krshna, Hare Krshna ♪
♪ Krshna Krshna Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Rama ♪
需要我帮忙吗
Should I be doing something?
♪ Rama Rama ♪
你保证我不会离开
You make sure I don't leave!
♪ Hare Krshna, Hare Krshna ♪
♪ Krishna Krshna, Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Rama, Hare Rama ♪
♪ Rama Rama, Hare Hare ♪
♪ Hare Krshna, Hare Krshna ♪
要吃点什么吗
Hey, do you need anything?
我可以给你拿点东西吃
I can bring you something to eat.
至少有东西能吐
Something to throw up.
你慢慢来
I'll give you time,
但是三号和四号房需要清理
but three and four need to be turned
床单也得叠
and the sheets need folding.
你就不能让我休息一下吗
Can't you give me a fucking break?
别吼我啊
Hey, don't be yelling at me.
记得三号和四号房
Three and four.
三号和四号
好好好好
Oh, alright, alright, alright.
我把所有床单都叠好了
I folded all them sheets.
我这是单人阅兵队啊
I'm a one man parade.
那是什么
What is that?
我这里有牛肉饼和土豆泥
I got Salisbury steak with mashed potatoes
以及烤火鸡胸肉和馅料
and roast turkey breast and stuffing.
你想吃什么
What would you like to eat?
我吃牛肉饼吧
I'll have a Salisbury steak.
好嘞这位女士 那请问您要怎么料理呢
Yes, ma'am. How would you like that cooked?
那到热档位怎么样
How about just hot?
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚需要我留着吗
So did you want me to stay here again?
好
Okay.
你有吃东西吗
Did you eat something?
吃过了 谢谢
I did, thank you.
这样吧
Ya know?
你今晚还是回去比较好
I think you'd better leave.
得了吧 我都被你骗一周了
Oh, come on, I been hearing you all week.
是有些其他“原因”
It's the other end.
啊对 也是
Oh, geez, alright.
总之有需要的话 找我就行
Well, if you need anything, let me know.
好
Yeah.
嗯
Okay.
给我走开不然我就叫警察了
Go away or I'll call the police.
你的肚子还难受吗
How's your tummy?
我是真的不太想和你说这事的
You know, I don't really wanna talk about that with you.
但谢谢你的药
But thank you for the pills.
那是罗亚尔提出来的
That was Royal's idea.
那我明天再谢谢他
Well, I'll thank him tomorrow.
睡不着吗
Couldn't sleep, huh?
嗯 还有我想告诉你
Nope, and I wanted to tell you
你工作做的很好
that you're doing good work.
客房都很干净 住客也很高兴
The place looks real clean and the guests are real happy.
谢谢老天爷 我做到了 我是合格的女仆了
Thank the Lord, I did it. I'm a maid.
是啊 罗亚尔爸爸去世的时候
Yeah, so when Royal's daddy died
把这个地方留给他 我刚好也住在这里
and left him the place, I was already staying here.
然后他问我要不要帮忙经营
So he asked me if I would help him run it.
等下 这是罗亚尔的旅店？
Wait, this is Royal's motel?
是他的
It is.
你们两不是一起长大的吗
Didn't you grow up together?
真是 我们没走一条道啊
Damn, we ain't run in the same circles.
也许还是好事呢
Well, that's probably better off,
因为他不知道为什么磕了很多迷幻药
'cause somehow he did so much LSD
导致大脑造成了永久损伤
that it permanently rewired his brain.
我说真的
I'm serious.
他可以正常生活 但是
I mean, he can function, but man,
你让他记得付账单的话 那就不行了
you ask him to remember to pay a bill?
所以 我有了住的地方和不多的薪水
So, I get a room and a small wage.
你在这之前是做什么的
And what'd you do before this?
我没做过什么
I never did much.
我以前在油田工作 后来离婚了
I worked the oil field and got divorced.
所以让我经营旅店？
So run a motel?
那我一定接
Sure, I'll do it.
你留着的那张照片 是你前妻吗
And that picture you keep, is that your ex-wife?
不是 那是我女儿 柏妮丝和她孩子
No, that is my daughter, Bernice and her baby.
你和她们分开了？
Did you leave them?
没有 是和妻子分开了
No, I left my wife.
我一有机会就会去见她们
I see them as much as possible.
就住在一小时路程远的地方
They live about an hour away from here.
发展的不顺利 是吗
Just didn't work out, huh?
她酗酒
Well, she drank.
但她打败了酒瘾
And she beat the drinking.
那个没关心过的教堂帮了她
And the church that helped her, I did not care for.
她很喜欢那教堂 更喜欢那牧师
And she liked the church and like the pastor more.
- 不是吧  - 没错
- No. - Yes.
牧师抢了我老婆
Preacher stole my wife.
写成歌一定会大卖
That's a gold record right there.
你觉得韦伦会唱吗?
You think Willie would sing it?
我觉得他早就唱过
I think he sang about it.
我估计也是
Yeah, I think he did.
你女儿呢?
And your girl?
是个好孩子
A good kid.
跟男人有些纠葛 你们都一样
Had troubles with men, like y'all do,
但最后结局是好的
but she turned out good, though.
我没有暗示
Hey, I didn't mean nothing
说是她的酗酒导致了我们离婚
by saying her drinking led to our divorce.
确实有这个原因 但她不是你
It did, but she ain't you
也没有哪两个人走的路是一模一样的
and things don't go the same way for any two people.
我不会因为你有同样的困扰
And I don't think any less of you
而对你产生偏见
for having the problems you do.
所以 我之前想问你
So, hey, I wanted to ask you
愿不愿意跟我和罗亚尔一起去舞会
if you wanted to join me and Royal at a dance.
现在你不想问了?
Now you don't wanna ask me no more?
我正在问啊 但这是全镇一起的活动
No, I am, I'm asking you, but it's a town thing.
全镇一起的活动?
It's- A town thing?
没错
Yeah, right.
意味着所有人都会去
Meaning, everyone will be there.
整个镇子
The whole town and...
行吧 那还是算了
Yeah, no thank you.
我只想说
I'm just saying that
这也是你的家
it's your home too.
如果你想做些除了
And if you're planning on doing something
跟我们俩看电视吃速食之外的事
other than eating TV dinners with me and the space cadet,
也许你该尝试冒冒险
maybe you oughta venture out a bit.
我是这么想的
That's all I'm thinking.
外公!
Paw-paw!
哇 是谁在喊我呀?
Oh, who's that yelling at me?
小贝琪 你好吗?
Hey, Betsey-girl, how you doing?
妈妈说我们可以玩游戏
Mom said we can play games.
她这么说吗?
Oh, she did, did she?
嘿 爸爸
Hey, dad.
嘿 你怎么样 你妈妈来吗?
Hey, how you doing? Is your mom coming?
不来 今天是礼拜日
No, it's Sunday.
上帝不许她来陪孙女出来玩
Lord forbid she have some fun with her granddaughter.
没事 我多得多占了
That's okay, more for me!
我跟贝琪说你能陪她玩游戏
I told Betsey you'd play games with her.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
不去哪
Nowhere.
那就好
Well, good.
柏妮丝 这位是莱斯利
Hey Bernice, this is Leslie.
罗亚尔雇她在旅馆当招待
Royal hired her on at the hotel, to host.
莱斯利 这是我女儿 柏妮丝
Leslie, this is my daughter, Bernice,
还有这位梦一样的孩子 是贝琪
and this little dream here, this is Betsey.
- 嗨!  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi!
很高兴认识你们俩
Well, pleasure to know you both.
很高兴认识你
It's nice to meet you.
咱们去玩吧?
Wanna get cracking?
- 好耶  - 我们走吧
- Yeah. - Alright, let's go.
你是这里的人吗?
Are you from around here?
没错 土生土长
Yep, born and raised.
你呢?
And what about you?
我们就在阿比林市附近
We're just outside of Abilene.
是吗 那边挺好
Ah, yeah, it's nice.
还行吧
Not too bad.
好耶 我领先了
Yeah, I'm winning.
我领先了哦
I'm winning.
我领先了
噢 不
Oh, no.
好耶
Oh, yeah.
天啊
Man.
- 真好  - 你女儿真棒
- It's nice. - Your girls are great.
我带得不错 是吧
I did alright, huh?
确实
Yes, you did.
- 你作弊  - 是啊 大家都作弊
- You cheated. - Yeah, they are cheaters.
- 嘿 我可没作弊  - 来吧
- Hey, I didn't cheat. - Come on.
- 走啦  - 走吧
- Come on. - Come on.
我们去玩下一项
Let's go to the next game.
这是什么?
What is this?
贝琪 看莱斯利送你什么了?
Hey, Betsey, look what Leslie got ya.
你接得住吗?
Can you catch?
- 接得住  - 能接住吗?
- Yeah. - Can you catch?
怎么回事?
What was that?
- 该死  - 那是什么
- Shit! - What was that?
- 给你  - 谢谢 达奇
- Here you go. - Thanks there, Dutch.
斯威尼 你好吗?
Sweeney, how are ya?
陪我家女孩们出来玩 你呢?
Just hanging out with my girls. And you?
没啥可抱怨的
Can't complain.
小莱
Lee.
嘿 达奇
Hey, Dutch.
♪ I was drivin' through Georgia in late July ♪
♪ On a day hot enough to make the devil sigh ♪
♪ I saw a homemade sign writtin' in red ♪
♪ Rhine County Watermelon Festival ahead ♪
他为了能陪孩子 她妈妈可是
The shovels of shit her mama made him eat
让他吃了不少亏
just to be there for his kid.
该给他颁个奖 是不是
He deserves a medal, huh?
男人也都不同以往了
Men ain't what they was.
我老爹一辈子打拼 就为给我们一个屋檐
My daddy worked whole life to give us a roof.
他只有八根手指头
He had eight fingers.
我老爹有十根 但他也努力了
Well, mine had 10, but he worked.
现在所有人都认为自己应该
Now everyone thinks they should be living
过电影里那种生活
some life out the movies.
人生艰难 不要再假装轻松了
Life is hard, stop acting like it ain't.
做好该做的 不伤害别人就行了
Just do what you gotta and don't hurt no one.
对于登月你怎么看?
What do you think about the moon landing?
什么?
What?
我们就去过一次
We only went there one time.
嘿
Hey.
你可以拍张照 能看得更久
You wanna take a picture, it'll lasts longer.
你真的中过彩票吗?
Is it true you won the lottery?
是的
Yes, I did.
你的奖金是怎么花的?
What did you do with all the money?
我买了个动物园
I bought a pettin' zoo.
我听说奖金都被你拿去嗑药了
I heard you put it up your nose.
你真的中过彩票吗?
Is it true you won the lottery?
是有人教你来这么说的吗?
Someone tell you to come say that?
赶紧走开
Get outta here.
不然跟你妈妈告状
Before I tell your mama what you're doing.
皮特家的女儿
Pete's girl.
是吗?
Yeah?
你想跳舞吗?
Hey, you wanna dance?
我想走了
I think I'm gonna go.
但谢谢你 给我愉快的一天
But thank you for a nice day.
等等 我们才刚到啊
Wait, we just got here.
发生什么事了吗?
Did something happen?
♪ Saw your picture in the paper ♪
皮特在搞她
Pete's been teasing her
嘿 别多管闲事
Hey, mind your business.
别这样 谁管他啊
Come on, who cares.
我们跳舞吧
Let's dance.
我确实挺喜欢这首歌
Well, I do like this song.
来就是了
That's it.
♪ All the things I never could ♪
我知道你是怎么想的
I know what you think about it.
♪ But I know that he can't give you ♪
♪ What you need most of all ♪
♪ So the door is always open ♪
这还不赖 是不是?
It's not so bad, right?
什么 跟你跳舞吗?
What? Dancing with you?
我们没跳多久 还不好判断
We ain't done it long enough for me to form an opinion.
不用担心我
Don't worry about me.
好吧
Alright.
我是指跟你一起出来
I'm talking about being out.
行吧 看来我能撑过去
Yeah, I suppose I'll survive.
大家 我中奖了!
I won ya'll!
我中奖了!
I just won.
I won!
这么多钱你要怎么花?
What you gonna do with all that money?
我要花一半钱买醉
I'ma drink my ass off with half of it
再拿另一半擦屁股!
and wipe my ass with the other!
你的孩子怎么办?
What about your kids?
孩子? 喝起酒谁管孩子!
Kids? I got drinks to drink!
走吧 我陪你
Come on, I'll come with you.
演得好啊 皮特
That's good, Pete.
真是不错
Real good.
这婊子还鼓掌呢
This bitch is clapping!
我不知道你在说什么 小莱
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about, Les.
我刚中了彩票
See, I just won the lottery.
世界不是围着你转的
Not everything's about you.
是吗? 你要怎么花奖金?
You did? What you gonna do with the money?
我能想出来的 你不用担心
I'll figure something, don't you worry.
只是不希望你把奖金浪费
I just wanna make sure you don't waste it
就像你浪费你的人生一样
like you wasted your goddamn life.
你还讲起笑话了
Oh, you got jokes, huh?
你个蠢婊 挥霍了十八万
You blew 180,000, you dumb bitch.
十九万 也不算多少
190, and it ain't that much.
那你呢 皮特?
And what about you, Pete?
我当初认识你 你才十八岁
When I first met you, you were fucking 18.
准备见识大千世界
You were ready to see the world.
现在再看看你
Look at you now.
你本可以有大好前程 但你落得这幅田地
You could've did anything, Pete, but you fucking did this.
所以不要跟我来这套
So don't give me your shit.
嘿 要不我们还是
Hey, hey, why don't we all just go back
开开心心玩吧
to having a good time?
好吗 算了吧
Huh? Come on.
斯威尼 你知道她干了什么吗?
You know what she did, Sweeney?
那不关我事
It's not my business,
也不用你在这里说教
it's not yours to be doing this here.
能不能知趣一点?
I mean, have some sense, alright?
我们玩得正开心呢
I mean, we're having fun.
你要是想睡她 最好搞清楚这些事
You oughta know if you're gonna be laying down with her.
达奇在哪?
Where's Dutch?
来个人送她回家吧
Someone needs to take her home.
你知道她丢下自己的孩子吗?
You know she left her kid?
他什么都不知道
- He don't know anything. - Hey.
嘿  嘿 别跟罗亚尔生气啊
Hey, hey, hey, no, no, don't get mad at Royal.
他只是想帮你
He's just trying to help you out.
她有没有告诉你 她把钱都用在买醉上
Did she tell you she drank all that money away?
一切机会 都让她白白浪费了
Had every chance, pissed it down the gutter,
- 还有她儿子  - 南希
and her son- Nancy.
抛下他 没留下一句话
Left him, no note, nothing.
那孩子才十三岁
That boy was 13.
没饭吃 怕得要命
Ain't have food, he's just scared.
没有妈妈 他无依无靠
He's all alone without his mama.
你倒是在外花天酒地 自以为是明星
Just so you could go out drinking, thinking you're hot shit.
不是那样的
That ain't fucking true.
都是爹生娘养出来的
Good Christian people raised you right.
你却毁了那男孩的一辈子
And you ruined that sweet boy's life.
那你又为什么没阻止我?
And what did you do to fucking stop me?!
- 去你妈的  - 去你妈 去你妈
- Fuck you. - Fuck you! Fuck you!
赶紧滚吧 贱人
Get her outta here. Bitch.
嘿 那些都是真的吗?
Hey, hey, was all that true?
怎么了 你要开除我?
So what? You wanna fire me?
莱斯利
Leslie.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
没事的 你尽力了
It's fine. You tried.
- 等等  - 我不怪任何人
- Just stop. - I don't blame anyone.
- 停一下好吗  - 怎么了?
- Just stop. - Why?
我当时很高兴能松口气
I was happy to have a break.
我确实玩乐了一阵 但我没想都花光的
Okay, I partied and I didn't mean to spend it all.
我失去了一切 甚至申请破产
I lost everything and I had to file for bankruptcy.
所有人都恨我
- Okay. - Fucking everyone hated me.
我房子也没了
I lost my place.
没错 我丢下了他
And so yeah, I left him.
好吗
Okay.
我离开了他
I left him.
好吧 我去道个别 然后送你回去
Okay, let me just say bye and I'll drive you.
好吗
Yeah.
嘿 没事的
Hey, it's fine.
莱斯利 我觉得你现在不该独处
Just, I don't think you should be alone, Leslie.
那是什么?
What's that?
我能给你打打气吗?
Do you mind if I lift your spirits?
有个兄弟在电视台工作
Got a buddy who works down at the station,
给我翻出来了这个
and he dug this up for me.
这里是奥贝酒吧
And it was here at Obe's honky ton-
看看你啊
- Look at you.
一个单身母亲中了大奖
That a single mother picked the winning numbers
交过税之后 就能带着
which after taxes, will be sending her home
改变人生的财富回家
with a life-changing sum of money.
莱斯利 感觉如何?
Leslie, how does it feel?
比昨天的心情好了一万倍
Well, I feel helluvalot better than yesterday.
我知道你选数字时
I understand that you had a little help
得到了一点小帮助
picking the winning numbers?
我永远都选同样的数字
I picked the same ones I always do.
数字是你儿子的生日吗?
And that was your son's birthday?
没错 詹姆斯 我儿子詹姆斯
Yeah, James, my son James.
你想见他吗?
You wanna meet him?
- 当然啊 -好
- Sure. - Okay.
詹姆斯 快过来
James! Come here.
这就是我儿子
This is my boy.
他幸运得很 而且超级可爱
Yeah, he's twice as lucky, half as cute.
你打算用这十九万大钞
And what do you plan to do
做什么呢?
with 190,000 smackeroos?
我也不知道
God, I don't know.
大概买栋房子吧 再给我儿子买点好的
Maybe by a house, buy something nice for my boy.
好好享受人生
Just have a better life!
小莱 那我们呢
Hey, Lee, what about us?
还有我们呢?
What about us?
酒我请了!
Drinks are on me!
詹姆斯 你有没有什么特别的东西
And you James, is there something special
是妈妈承诺你的?
that momma owes you now?
怎么 生下你还不够吗?
What? Being born ain't enough?
一把吉他 我要做下一个韦伦
A guitar, so I can be the next Waylon.
不错啊
Oh, yeah.
我还希望她开一家餐厅
And I want her to open a diner.
她一直想开餐厅
She always wanted a diner.
你会起名"莱斯利餐厅"吗?
Hey, well, would you call it Leslie's?
我希望能在开业那天去捧场
Well, I hope to be there on opening day.
我们期待你到临
Well, we're looking forward to ya.
好了 来自第十频道新闻全体的祝贺
Alright, well, from all of us at Channel 10 News;
恭喜莱斯利!
here's to Leslie!
致以最诚挚的祝福
We wish you all the best.
我得再看一遍 你看起来棒极了
Oh, I'm gonna watch that again, you look so good!
不 不
No, no.
倒一下带
Just gonna rewind it.
我说我不想再看一遍了 该死
I said I don't wanna watch it again, goddammit.
我都说了不要 如果你一开始就我说的话
I said no, if you just listened the first time,
就不会这么伤感情了
then you wouldn't get your feelings hurt.
我只是觉得这样挺好...
I just thought it'd be nice to...
出去
Get out.
别啊 我只是觉得
Hey, come on, I just thought it'd be nice
能一起看看 让你想起
if we watch it together just to remind you
你并非大家所说的
that you're not the piece of shit
那么一无是处
that everybody says you are.
我看到一个深爱儿子的好妈妈
Right, what I saw was a good mama loving on her boy,
看来我是没考虑周全
but I guess I wasn't thinking.
你确实没考虑周全
No, you weren't thinking.
你按自己的方式介入我的人生 我跟你说
You're shoving your way into my life and you know what?
这是我的人生
It's my life.
上帝啊 这一周真不顺!
Jesus Christ, this fucking week!
录像带的事我很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry I got the fucking tape thing.
你居然还敢骂我!
Don't you fucking swear at me!
他...
He...
他再也不会跟我说话了
He ain't never gonna speak to me again.
我的家人都不愿意跟我联络了
My folks don't wanna fucking speak to me,
全镇的人都像躲瘟神一样躲着我
and everyone in town tries to avoid me like the plague,
我的儿子也不愿意见我
and my boy doesn't wanna see me.
我被困在这 跟你和罗亚尔一起
And I'm fucking stuck here with you and Royal,
两个臭皮匠 简直是给我失败人生上
pair of fucking hilljacks like the shit icing
再添两道败笔
on my shit fucking life.
你知道吗
Ya know?
遇到我和罗亚尔算是你的福气了
Me and Royal are the best thing that happened to you.
所以不要骂人
So don't call us names.
你的家人不跟你联络
And your family won't talk to you
也是你的行为带来的后果
because they shouldn't after what you did.
但你还活着 对吧?
But you're living, right?
很抱歉这不是童话世界
I'm sorry it ain't a fairy tale.
我们都有后悔的时候
We all should have done things differently.
但你人生的问题出在你身上 跟别人无关
But you're what's wrong with your life, not anyone else.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
好吧
Okay
好了 坐下 莱斯利
Alright, just sit down, Leslie.
去你妈
Fuck you.
别这样 我们谈谈
Come on, let's just talk about it.
你要去哪里? 你要做什么?
Where are you gonna go? What are you gonna do?
我知道你要去哪
I know where you're gonna go.
然后你做出的一切努力
And everything you did to get better
就全都白搭了
is just gonna be gone.
这不需要你担心
Well, it ain't you're concern.
因为我他妈不干了！
'Cause I fucking quit!
您好 现在您拨打的电话
Hello, no one is available
无人接听
to take your call at this time.
请在嘀声后留言
Please leave a message after the tone.
詹姆斯 是我
James, it's me.
对你做的事我很抱歉
I'm so sorry for what I did to you.
我非常非常爱你
I love you so much, and uh...
我爱你 甜心
I love you sweetie.
多少钱?
How much?
七块 但给你熟人价 七块钱就行
Seven, but for you we'll say seven.
我认为自己喝闷酒是一种罪过
I think drinking alone's a mortal sin.
这杯要敬什么?
We toasting to something?
没什么好敬的
Nothing good.
你真是 世间尤物
You are gorgeous.
就敬这个吧
I'll drink to that.
来吧
Go ahead.
你为什么来跟我搭讪?
Why did you come and talk to me?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我身上有什么让你青睐吗?
Did you see something in me you like?
有啊 一小时后 我会
I do. Me, in about an hour.
那可太好了
Oh, that's good.
女士 如果你没兴趣 直说就好
If you ain't interested, you just say so, lady.
来吧 跟我说说
Come on, tell me.
你在我身上看到什么特别之处了?
Did you see something special in me?
还是觉得拿下我轻轻松松?
Or did you see a sure thing?
我觉得你...
I think you're...
我觉得我是在等别人
I think I'm waiting on someone else.
是我有心事让你没兴趣了是吗
Lots of fun until I got something on my mind, huh?
这个 如果你想 我们可以聊天
I guess, I can talk to you if you want.
我猜你非常会聊天
Oh, I bet you can talk real good.
我猜你 能把我夸到天上去
I bet you can tell me how beautiful I am.
你想的话
If you want.
告诉我说我没事
Tell me I'm good.
告诉我说 我不是一无是处
Tell me I ain't a piece of shit.
你不是的
You ain't.
你没事的
You're good.
你有车吗 先生？
You got a car, mister?
她去哪了?
Well, where did she go?
我怎么知道？ 斯维尼
How the hell I know, Sweeney?
该死的！
Goddammit!
斯威尼 你好吗?
Sweeney, how are you?
别挡我的道
Get out of my way.
你找小莱的话 在这就对了
If you're looking for Lee, this is the place.
你什么毛病啊?
What is wrong with you, woman?
你改变不了她的
You ain't gonna change her.
让我过去 皮特
Just get out of my way, Pete.
你能不能别挡我的道?
Why don't you get out of my way?
小子 注意点
Watch it, boy.
我这小子能胖揍你
This boy'll whoop your ass.
- 打他!  -  该死的!
- Hit him! - Goddammit!
皮特 打他 打他
Hit him, Pete. Hit him.
该死 滚!
Damn it, get!
妈的 我要杀了他!
Shit! I'll kill him!
你才多大能耐 臭小子
You ain't gonna do shit, you little pissant.
乖乖坐下 闭嘴
Sit down and shut up.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
去你全家 我这是在维护你们
Fuck all y'all, I was standing up for y'all
要不这样吧 下一轮皮特请客!
Guess what y'all? Next round's on Pete!
行 都给我喝便宜货吧 混蛋们
Yeah, drink your Coors Light on me, assholes!
嘿 伯特
Hey Bert,
她要是不回来了
if she ain't coming back,
介意我来解决这两杯小可爱吗
you mind if I give these lovely children a home?
要命吗 姐啊
Goddamn it, woman!
你是喝多了吗?
Have you been drinking?
没有
No.
我不知道你认为自己在干嘛
Well, I don't even know what you think you're doing
因为我们之间已经没话好说了
because there's no conversation between us
除非你开始道歉
till you start apologizing.
我要那家冰淇淋店
I want the ice cream shop.
什么? 就那个?
What? That?
我这辈子花了太多时间
I spent too much of my life
跟我甚至不认识的人躲在一起
hiding with people I don't even know.
我已经躲够了
And I'm done with hiding
我也不想再被抛弃了
and I'm sure as shit done with being run off.
所以你打算住在那里?
So you're gonna live in there?
我打算把它翻新 你也要帮忙
I'm gonna make something out of it and you're gonna help!
你为什么一直吼我?
Why are you yelling at me?
因为我很亢奋 给我拿把锤子!
Because I'm excited! Get me a hammer!
什么 你以为你能随意使唤我吗
Wait, you think you can just tell me what to do
你还骂过我
after you called me names-
给我拿把锤子
- Get me a hammer.
好吧
Okay.
当心!
Watch out!
当心有钉子
Oh, watch out for nails.
好了 就这样了
Alright, this is it.
需要帮忙吗?
You need help?
没事 我可以
No, I got it.
你知道这是罗亚尔父亲的店吧
You know this is Royal's daddy's, right?
- 知道  - 他认为
- Yeah. - He thought it'd
这会在小孩子中大受欢迎 但没成功
be a real hit with the kids, but didn't work out.
在这里废弃了四十年了
Now it's just been sitting here, like, 40 years
等待有人能给它打一针强心剂
just waiting for someone to give it shot.
打一针破伤风 或者乙肝疫苗吧
Yeah, like a tetanus shot or a hepatitis shot.
听着 我看过视频 我知道你对此很兴奋
Look, I saw that video and I know you're excited about this,
但是 对于经营这种地方
but I mean, what do you know
你懂多少呢?
about running a place like this?
这个 你对经营旅馆又懂些什么呢?
Well, what'd you know about running a motel?
我是认真的 好吗?
No, I'm serious, alright?
除非你藏着什么
I mean, unless you're hiding some
其他的绝招
other jackpot somewhere,
你得有台炸锅 还得有个烤炉
I mean, you gotta get a fryer, you gotta get a grill.
这都很贵的
That's expensive.
然后你还要聘个厨子 还要制作菜单
And then you gotta hire a cook and you gotta make menus,
你得弄台汽水机器 还得有
you gotta get a soda machine, you gotta get-
这建议都挺好啊 你要来这工作吗?
- Hey, that's very good, do you wanna work here?
我知道你很兴奋
All right. I mean, I understand that you're excited,
但说真的 你打算怎么负担这些费用?
but honestly, how are you planning on paying for this?
你不能要求涨薪 涨不了
I mean, you can't ask us for a raise 'cause we can't,
我们没钱
we don't have it.
怎么了?
What?
我会搬过来和你同居
I'm gonna move in with you.
我能攒钱
I can save.
我可以在周末兼职
I can work on weekends.
可能要花个十年 但就这么办吧
Hey, it might take 10 years, but let's do it.
好啊
Okay.
好吗?
Yeah?
这个 得征求罗亚尔同意
Well, I mean, I gotta ask Royal.
但你会问他的对吧?
But you gonna ask him?
会的 我去问他
Yeah, yeah, I'll ask him.
天啊
Damn
你为什么对我这么好?
Why are you so good to me?
这个嘛
Well
我认为现在答案很明显了
I think it's pretty obvious by now.
好吧
Okay.
那我们有事要忙了?
So we got work to do?
- 等会再说  - 好吧
- Later. - Okay.
（十个月后）
好了 地板看起来不错
Alright, floors are lookin' good.
说不好 我觉得该再擦一遍
I don't know, I think we should mop em again.
你在拖延呢
Oh, you're stalling.
罗亚尔 我们玩真的了!
Royal, we're doing this!
我抖得像片叶子
I'm shakin' like a goddamn leaf.
还是觉得名字该叫"皇家(罗亚尔)餐厅"
Still think we shoulda called the place "Royal's."
穿上制服 搞夸张点
Put on some costumes, do it up big.
我才不要穿成公主
I ain't dressing up like a goddamn princess.
我知道了 搞几个骑士 还有魔怪
I know, a couple of knights and a bridge troll.
我挺喜欢
I like it.
顾客喜欢主题餐厅
People like themes.
我都说不搞了 闭嘴好吗?
I said no, okay? Shut up.
来真的了
Here we go.
点餐!
Order up!
这就好了
Here we go.
好冷清啊
Well, it's pretty quiet.
我们开业刚一分钟
We've been open a minute,
一分钟都没到
not even.
去他们的
Fuck 'em.
我都不知道自己何必要这样了
Well, I don't know why I'm doing this, anyway.
都没那么重要了
Why it even matters.
他们就是恶毒
They're just being mean.
他们总要吃饭的
They'll have to eat.
他们会来的 来了就知道了
They'll come, they'll see.
我得抽根烟
I need a cigarette.
我们打烊了!
We're closing up!
怎么...
What the...
来了 可算来了
Oh, here we go, it's about time.
罗亚尔 来人了
Royal, we got one.
就说我们打烊了
Well, tell 'em we're closed.
小莱 有顾客
Lee, it's a customer.
他们白天怎么不来 我要回家了
No, they've had all day, I'm going home.
- 嘿 小莱  - 怎么了?
- Hey, Lee. - What?
你最好从后门溜走
Maybe you oughta slip out the back.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
你去后门
You go to the back.
没事 我来 没关系
No, I got it, it's fine.
- 去吧  - 我来就行
- Go on. - No, I got it.
去吧
Go on.
好吧
Okay.
拿着这个
Take this.
欢迎来到小莱餐厅 请问要点什么?
Welcome to Lee's, how can I help you?
你好 两位
Two please.
这里就行
Just right here.
桌子不能坐吗?
What's wrong with a table?
已经预定了 会员专属
Well, that's reserved. For members.
今晚达奇不和你一起吗?
So will Dutch be joining you tonight?
- 不  - 好吧
- No. - Okay.
我给你拿张菜单来
Well, I'll just get a menu for you then
我这就去
I'll just...
你来得有点晚了 所以得快点
You're a little late, so you wanna be quick
不然后厨就熄火了
before we close the grill.
小莱 你能收敛一点吗?
Lee, you wanna pull it back just a little?
你做到了 南希
You did it, Nance.
没有一个人来
No one came.
恭喜 你真是给我上了一课
Congratulations, you sure fucking showed me.
小姑娘
Little girl-
看在上帝的份上
- I mean, Jesus fucking Christ,
你就不能提前一年搞我吗?
couldn't you done this like a year ago?
你眼看着我做了一切努力
You watched me do all this
明知要从我这里夺走一切
knowing you're gonna take it away from me.
我们曾是家人
We was family.
你到底有多恶毒?
How fucking mean are you?
对于一切我很抱歉
I'm sorry for what happened.
听到没? 我很抱歉
Do you hear me? I'm sorry.
你是对的 我早该阻止你
And you were right, I could have stopped you.
我看到了一切的发生
I saw what was happening,
我早该阻止 但我没有
I could have stopped it and I didn't.
因为我只顾着玩乐
'Cause I was having fun.
那么多晚上 你让我抱着那个小男孩
But for all the nights you made me hold that little boy,
那么多次 你逼着我说谎
all the times you made a liar out of me
我是唯一一个跟他讲
when I was the only one telling him,
别听那些人说话
"Don't you listen to them people."
我了解你妈妈
I know your mama.
她太爱你 不会这样做的
"She loves you too much to do you like this."
你不该离开的
You shouldn't have left.
我不管你有多失败 看起来有多蠢
I don't care how bad you fucked up, how stupid you looked,
那小男孩爱过你
that little boy loved you.
我们都爱过你
We all did.
这一点我绝不会原谅你
I ain't never gonna forgive you for that.
我也没有请求你的原谅
And I don't ask you to forgive me,
但我想我们都互相折磨够了
but I think we've all done enough suffering.
谢谢你
Thank you.
是啊
Yeah.
现在
Now
把脸擦擦
wipe your face and
转过头去
turn your head.
什么?
What?
我的天啊
Oh my God.
我要两份特餐
I'll take two of them specials and
希望你不要往里面吐口水
I'd appreciate it if you didn't spit in 'em.
两份特餐 不要口水
Two specials, hold the spit.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
- 还好  - 好吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
我得坐这里吧
I guess I'll sit here.
当然 请坐
Sure, yeah.
嘿 你怎么样?
Hey, how you doing?
我是斯威尼
Sweeney.
我是詹姆斯 很高兴认识你
James, nice to meet you.
幸会 幸会
Yeah, nice to meet you.
你是一路开车过来的?
So did you drive all the way down here?
是的
I did.
好的
Okay.
你饿了吗?
Are you hungry?
饿了
I am.
好的 好的
Okay, alright.
让我去忙活下炸锅
Well, I'm just gonna fix this fryer,
也许回头我们能聊聊
but maybe we can chat it up later.
你说呢?
What do you think?
- 好啊  - 好的
- Yeah. - Alright.
那壶咖啡是新煮的
Just made that pot of coffee.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
你想来点咖啡吗?
Well, would you like some coffee?
- 谢谢你  - 好的
- Please. - Yeah, okay.
好喝又热乎
It's nice and hot.
煮得不错
Makes it good.
糖在这里
Sugar's here.
好的 谢谢
Alright, thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
两份特餐新鲜出炉
Okay, two specials comin' in hot.
意面豆子汤
Okay, pasta fazool.
请问有餐具吗?
You got any silverware?
天啊 有的
Oh God, yes.
拿到了
Got it.
我就 留你慢慢享用
I'll just leave you to it.
这里有盐和胡椒
This is salt and pepper.
好的 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
妈妈
Mom.
怎么了?
Yeah?
很好吃
It's great.
宝贝 我好想你
I missed you, baby...
我衣服蹭到意面了
I've got pasta on my shirt.
天啊 我太想你了
Oh, God, I missed you.
是啊
Yeah.
宝贝
Oh, baby.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
♪ To save my soul I ran through the night ♪
♪ Got lost in the woods and found Jesus ♪
♪ Another morning, another regret ♪
♪ Cursing the demons lying in bed ♪
♪ Angels are falling down on me ♪
（小莱餐厅）
♪ Angels keep falling down on me ♪
♪ Chasing the pavement, hiding the cracks ♪
♪ Been here so long don't know how to get back ♪
♪ Been down this road, not gonna lie ♪
♪ Can't even tell you how many times ♪
♪ Angels are falling down on me ♪
♪ Windows are dirty, I can't see a thing ♪
♪ I don't know if this life goes anywhere ♪
♪ Try to be good, yeah you try to be real ♪
♪ Try to pretend that I know what I feel ♪
♪ Angels are falling down on me ♪
♪ Angels keep falling down on me ♪
♪ Don't walk away ♪
♪ You can count on me ♪
♪ Girl, where you going ♪
♪ What have you done ♪
♪ Seems like you're running from everyone ♪
♪ What happened to your dreams ♪
♪ Have they falling by your side ♪
♪ Will you just fade away, in the stone cold night ♪
♪ And never say goodbye ♪
♪ Never say goodbye ♪
♪ 'Cause you're lost somewhere inside ♪
♪ But there's nowhere left to hide ♪